Guide to the Miscellaneous popular fiction collection, 1944-1992
Miscellaneous popular fiction collection, 1944-1992
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Miscellaneous popular fiction collection, 1944-1992
7691
171 v., comprising 2.8 cubic ft.
Printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Erotic and pornographic novels in the pulp paperback format on a variety of subjects including swinging, bisexuality, sadomasochism, incest, and bestiality.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Erotic and pornographic novels in the pulp paperback format on a variety of subjects including swinging, bisexuality, sadomasochism, incest, and bestiality.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Bestiality.; Bisexuals.; Incest.; Non-monogamous relationships.; Popular literature.; Sadomasochism.
Form and Genre Terms:
Erotica.; Pornography.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Books are listed alphabetically by author. Title, publisher, series and series number if applicable (-0- if not), and date are also given.
CONTAINER LIST
- Aldiss, Brian W., The Hand-Reared Boy, New American Library Inc., T 4575, 1970 (Box 1)
- Allen, Ray, Lash of the Devil Jap, Bizarre Library, BL 44, n.d. (Box 1)
- Allison, Glenn, Quick Moves, Wee Hours Books, WH 519, 1966 (Box 1)
- Allison, Glenn, Season For Three, Wee Hours Inc., WH 508, 1966 (Box 1)
- Andrews, Terry, The Story of Harold, Avon Books, -0-, 1974 (Box 1)
- Anonymous, All In Knots, Star Distributors, BD-133, 1989 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Amy: Undercover, Star Distributors, SW-155, 1990 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Beaten Belinda (and Taffy is Trouble), Star Distributors, TCN5, 1989 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Beaten Belinda, Star Distributors, BY-137, n.d. (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Broken Bitch, Star Distributors, BD-140, 1989 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Cheerleader's Hot Panties, Star Distributors, HC-115, 1989 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, The Diary Of: Monique's Battered Slave, Star Distributors, PJ-104, 1978 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, How To Keep A Man, Star Distributors, FD-101, 1989 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Enema Resort, Star Distributors, FT-126, 1992 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Handcuffs for Hannah, Star Distributors, AB-108, 1992 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, House of Screaming Virgins, Star Distributors, BL 78, 1980 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Locked in Leather, Star Distributors, HYB-108, 1979 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Hogtied Heiress, Star Distributors, AB-107, 1992 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, Her Lesbian Cousin, Star Distributors, IJ-107, 1983 (Box 6)
- Anonymous, A Man With A Maid: Book Two, Grove Press, B-434, 1972 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, A Man With A Maid: Book Three, Grove Press, B-476, 1982 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Mistress's Revenge, Star Distributors, BT-127, 1990 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Nazi Experimental Victims, War Horrors, WA-524, n.d. (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Next Door Voyeur, Carlyle Communications, BL 5523-R, 1978 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Offbeat Sex: The Back Roads to Climax, Star Distributors, LL-73, 1975 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, The Pearl: A Journal of Voluptuous Reading (The Underground Magazine of Victorian England), Grove Press, B-155, 1968 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Ruled By Women, Star Distributors, WP105, 1992 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Sadistic Lesbian,, TWI-84, n.d. (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Secret Lives, Carroll & Graf, -0-, 1983 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Seductive Women: Mature Women & Young Girls, Star Distributors, LL-122, 1978 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Sex Education, Star Distributors, UT-103, 1982 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Shaming Her Panty-Clad Husband, Star Distributors, ER-132, 1980 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, She-Male Husband, Star Distributors, CD-11, 1980 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, School For Sex: Learning the Hard Way, Star Distributors, CB-121, 1975 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Tough Broads, Star Distributors, BT-144, 1992 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Training Lesbians in Chains, Star Distributors, Dis-139, 1980 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Transvestism: Forced To Be She-Males, Star Distributors, HFF-117, 1980 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, TV Soap Star, Star Distributors, TT-105, 1989 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, The Unforgiven Maiden, Monks Secret Library, MSL-10, n.d. (Box 7)
- Anonymous, The Way of a Man With a Maid, Victorian Classics Inc., VC103, 1967 (Box 7)
- Anonymous, Willing Slave, Star Distributors, BON-112, 1979 (Box 7)
- Arsan, Emmanuelle, Emmanuelle II, Grove Press, Inc., B-453, 1974 (Box 1)
- Banks, Ramond E., Ultimate Tranform, Orchid Publishing Co., CB 209, 1978 (Box 1)
- Baxter, Phyllis, Sugar Mama and Daddy, Trans-European Publications, TSS/808, 1975 (Box 1)
- Baxter, Shane V., The Virgin and the Monster, Olympia Press, Inc., OPH-243, 1971 (Box 1)
- Bedford, Clive, Barbarian Victim, Eros Publishing, BB-128, 1975 (Box 1)
- Bedford, Clive, Bondage Nightmare, Eros Publishing, BB-134, 1975 (Box 1)
- Bedford, Clive, Cage of Cruelty, Eros Publishing, BB-132, 1975 (Box 1)
- Bedford, Clive, The Slaves Revolt, Eros Publishing, BB-130, 1975 (Box 1)
- Borden, John, Sex Club, Tower Publications, 34-951, 1968 (Box 1)
- Brandon, Ralph, Witch Finder (w/ note by author on title page), Fabian Books Ltd., Z-134, 1960 (Box 1)
- Brown, Harry, Sadist's Dungeon, Bizarre Library, BL 41, n.d. (Box 1)
- Burch, Ralph, Lust In Space, Eros Publishing, TT 108, 1978 (Box 1)
- Burton, Edward, The Mouth Job, Aquarius Publishers, API-128, 1972 (Box 1)
- Caldwell, Vance, A Violent Woman, Trans-European Publications, TSS/823, 1975 (Box 2)
- Campbell, F.E., Chain Me Forever, H.O.M. Inc., H 143, 1983 (Box 2)
- Campbell, F.E., Dorinda, House of Milan Corp., H 110, 1977 (Box 2)
- Campbell, F.E., Melynda and Mister Wilberforce, House of Milan Corp., H 102, 1976 (Box 2)
- Campbell, F.E., Barbe Bound, HOM Inc., -0-, 1981 (Box 6)
- Campbell, F.E., The Prisoner of Ismaul, House of Milan, H-104, 1976 (Box 7)
- Campbell, F.E., The Prisoner of Ismaul: Volume 2, House of Milan, H 108, 1977 (Box 7)
- Cassill, R.V., My Sister's Keeper, Hearst Corporation, Avon Books, T-441, 1960 (Box 7)
- Ception, John V., Earth Sex in the 21st Century, Echelon Book Publishers, IL-533, 1970 (Box 2)
- Cousins, Sadie, Confessions of a Pervert, Griffon Enterprises, CP 505, 1968 (Box 2)
- Craft, Woody, Forced to Please, Wee Hours Books, WH 562, 1968 (Box 2)
- Crawford, Rebecca, A Brother's Revenge, Tiburon House Publishing Co., RAS-1408, 1973 (Box 2)
- Criterion, Mitchell, House of Illusions, Midwood Books, M-195-1, 1970 (Box 2)
- Crowder, E.C., The Transexuals, Oligarch Publishing Co., H 1002, 1969 (Box 2)
- Dean, Hathaway, Handbook of Perversions, Echelon Book Publishers, IL-361, 1969 (Box 2)
- Dickson, Jim E., Ring of Steel: The Diary of a Modern Slave, Eros Publishing, BP-117, 1983 (Box 2)
- Douglas, Jeff, The Balling Machine, Eros Publishing, 765-T, 1971 (Box 2)
- Eggers, Jason, The Police Girl, Tiburon House Publishing Co., LLP/312, 1973 (Box 2)
- Eidelberg, Ludwig, The Dark Urge, Pyramid Books, R607, 1961 (Box 2)
- Emmett, Stu, Her Incest Craving, Cameo Library, Inc., CC-224, 1975 (Box 2)
- Eros, Eden, Dog Job, Aquarius 7 Publishers, API-147, 1973 (Box 2)
- Faber, Arthur, Outerspace Sex Orgy, Barnaby Press, BP 110, 1970 (Box 2)
- Feinberg, Shari, Family Vengeance, Brighton Books, 339, 1977 (Box 2)
- Fingerhut, John, Mommy's Loving Son, Publisher's Consultants, DP 114, 1978 (Box 2)
- Fulton, Ward, Oral Fathers, American Art Enterprises, ORL-118, 1971 (Box 2)
- Gable, Paul, Bound for Torment, Greenleaf Classics, BH8032, 1977 (Box 2)
- Garber, Jeff, Her Three-Way Rape, Greenleaf Classics, BH8003, 1976 (Box 2)
- George, Elvis, Gang Mother, Liverpool Distributors, OLB/109, 1978 (Box 3)
- Gilmore, John, Brother Sister Bang, Eros Publishing, CLX 103, 1976 (Box 3)
- Goerfelt, Hans, Trained to Obey, Publisher's Consultants, FPS-115, 1979 (Box 3)
- Goodwood, Clement, The Red Whip, BB Sales Co., F-110, 1968 (Box 3)
- Gordon, Davis, Swastika Sex Cult, Corsair Publications, CB 214, 1968 (Box 3)
- Gray, Violet, Half-Cocked, Eros Publishing, CMB-104, 1975 (Box 3)
- Greene, Gerald and Caroline, S-M: The Last Taboo, Grove Press, B-376, 1974 (Box 3)
- Greene, Sean, The Leg Man, M-T Publishers Inc., RC 542, 1969 (Box 3)
- Hall, Mannie, Hard Knocks for Honey, Star Distributors, BBB-431, 1978 (Box 3)
- Handel, Will, Angel With a Whip, Star Distributors, WR-456, 1978 (Box 3)
- Hobart, Brian, The Cruelty Connection, Eros Publishing, BB-122, 1974 (Box 3)
- Hogar, Jackson, Palestinian Tormentors, Stag Books, PCB 114, 1977 (Box 3)
- Hunt, Mike, Bound to Obey, Kiowa Books Inc., 104, 1969 (Box 3)
- James, Antony, The Abnormal World of Transvestites and Sex Changes, LS Publications Corp., IMP 724, 1965 (Box 3)
- James, Antony, England's Sex Habits, LS Publications Corp., IMP 704, 1964 (Box 3)
- Jenson, Peter, Mother's New Boarder, Tiburon House Publishing Co., RWS/149, 1971 (Box 3)
- Johnson, Donald, The Nudists, Outdoor American Corp., -0-, 1959 (Box 3)
- Key, Michael, Lust Thrills, Bee-Line Books, 766-T, 1972 (Box 3)
- Kingsley, Charles W., Insex Mania, Nordisk Bladcentrals A/S, I 52, 1970 (Box 3)
- Lamont, Gil, The Watcher, Encounter Books, SL 122, 1978 (Box 3)
- Lefevre, Raoul, A Secret Torment, Tiburon Publishing House, BSS/738, 1974 (Box 3)
- Leighton, Russell, Journal of an Incestuous Father, Paramount Publishers, PPD 201-B, 1971 (Box 3)
- Long, Emil, Horny Hostage, Publisher's Consultants, JJ-113, 1981 (Box 3)
- Marks, Stefen, Torture Center Terror, Publisher's Consultants, RDB-110, 1977 (Box 7)
- Marr, Manuel, Whipped By Her Black Master, Star Distributors, ER 103, 1978 (Box 4)
- Marshall, Jeff, Terror Experiment, Bizarre Library, BL 42, n.d. (Box 4)
- Martin, Olivia, The Ultimate Orgy, American Art Enterprises, LL-104, 1985 (Box 4)
- Masters, Randi, The Rape Machine, American Art Enterprises, LL-102, 1985 (Box 4)
- McElroy, Winston, Gang Initiation, Tiburon House Publishing Co., LLP 210, 1970 (Box 4)
- McKenna, Pearl, The Dorm Mother, Surrey House, SC133, 1974 (Box 4)
- Mell, Stanislaus, Mister Sister, Bee Dee Publications, -0-, 1968 (Box 4)
- Mellows, Suzanne, The Sex-Ray, Tiburon House Publishing Co., LLP/349, 1973 (Box 4)
- Merrick, Geoffrey, Slaves to Rock 'n' Roll, HOM Inc., MWS 1, 1985 (Box 4)
- Merrick, Geoffrey, Bondage University, HOM Inc., MWS 5, 1987 (Box 4)
- Merrick, Geoffrey, Cult Captives, HOM Inc., MWS 7, 1987 (Box 4)
- Miller, Jessie, Whip Chick, Bee-Line Books, 5117T, 1972 (Box 4)
- Minton, Walter, Sexual Spanking and Bondage, Eros Publishing, PML-112, 1974 (Box 4)
- Moreno, Consuelo, Bondage Mad House, Tortura Press, TP-106, 1971 (Box 4)
- Parker, Peter, My Son, My Slave, Eros Publishing, BB-29, 1972 (Box 4)
- Paule, Ben, Cycle Sadist, Paramount Publisher, PP111, 1971 (Box 4)
- Peldt, Flossy, Sex Blow Out, Bee-Line Books, 774-T, 1972 (Box 4)
- Phillips, Nancy, Her Loving Group, Cameo Library, CC-222, 1975 (Box 4)
- Piombo, Akbar del, The Double-Bellied Companion, Olympia Press, TC-204, 1955 (Box 4)
- Ramsey, Chuck, Trapped & Tied Baby Hookers, Star Distributors Ltd., JN-1013, 1976 (Box 4)
- Raymond, Pete, Teacher's Crowded Bed, Tiburon Publishing House, SRS-1048, 1975 (Box 4)
- Reage, Pauline, Story of O, Grove Press, BB28913, 1965 (Box 4)
- Reage, Pauline, Story of O Part II, Grove Press, B-438, 1971 (Box 5)
- Rifkin, Shepard, Desire Island, Ace Books, D-444, 1960 (Box 5)
- Rockman, Peter, Bondage Sex Clubs, Eros Publishing, XL-104, 1976 (Box 5)
- Rufneck, Hannah, Her Desire For Discipline, Carlyle Communications, LL0348, 1978 (Box 5)
- Ruhr, S.C., Susan's Sex Trip, Bee-Line Books, BL 779-R, 1972 (Box 7)
- Savage, Frederick, The Emperor's Lash, Bizarre Library, BL 26, n.d. (Box 5)
- Schultz, W.T., The Slaves of Helga Borg, NP Inc., ORL 942, 1969 (Box 5)
- Seeds, William, Ripped to Shreds, Eros Publishing, CMB 126, 1977 (Box 5)
- Seeds, William, Suck My Urge, Eros Publishing, CMB-103, 1975 (Box 5)
- Shaffer, John, The Encounter Group, Tiburon House Publishing, RWS/132, 1970 (Box 5)
- Sharpe, Vera, Queen of Evil, Bizarre Library, BL 29, n.d. (Box 5)
- Shoal, William, Four-Legged Sex Partners, Copley Square Press, CSP-197, 1975 (Box 5)
- Simmons, Blake, A Naked Pile-Up, Tiburon House Publishing, BSS/758, 1974 (Box 5)
- Simmons, Blake, A Strange Appetite, Tiburon House Publishing, LLP/298, 1972 (Box 5)
- Smith, Leda, Leather Climax For Her Lover, Star Distributors, WM-2013, 1977 (Box 5)
- Star, Del, The Kingdom of Joy, Pyramid Books, A4025, 1976 (Box 5)
- Starr, Lance, The Fiery Hostess, New World Publishing Co., VL-114, n.d. (Box 5)
- Stencek, Pavel, Bondage: A How-To Guide for Enthusiasts, Eros Publishing, HT 101, 1977 (Box 5)
- Stephens, Brian, Steel-Studded Dildo, Bizarre Library, BL 47, n.d. (Box 5)
- Stephens, Ginger, The Nurse's Sex Dilemma, Star Distributors, BBB-416, 1977 (Box 5)
- Stone, Mitch, Bi-Sex Sucker, American Art Enterprises, GAY-101, 1984 (Box 5)
- Stone, Paul, Rape License, Eros Publishing, TB-101, 1975 (Box 5)
- Suade, Harrington, Sexual Prisonre, Echelon Book Publishers, IR-208, 1974 (Box 5)
- Sweet, Laurie, Used, Abused Little Runaway, Suree Limited, RX439, 1976 (Box 5)
- Thomas, Eric, Three Way Pain, Eros Publishing, BB-125, 1975 (Box 5)
- Towers, Charles, Nazi Nightmare Captive, Publisher's Consultants, SXB-123, 1977 (Box 5)
- Trainer, Russ, Artists and Models, Wizard Publications, WWNC 403, 1967 (Box 5)
- Trapper, Joseph T., Lonely is the Slave, American Art Enterprises, SNM-178, 1976 (Box 5)
- Trocchi, Alexander, Thongs, Brandon House, 6264, 1967 (Box 5)
- Van Heller, N., The Unholy Imprisonment, Liverpool Distributors, LLP/675, 1977 (Box 6)
- Vandemere, James E., The Adulterous Wife, Tiburon House Publishing Co., LLP/323, 1973 (Box 6)
- Various, Amazons II, Daw Books, DB 485, 1982 (Box 5)
- Vermont, Monica, Black and Wild, Liverpool Distributors, NRS/3006, 1977 (Box 6)
- Vickers, Robert, Daughter In Bondage, Greenleaf Classics, BC2003, 1978 (Box 6)
- Vickers, Robert, Sister in Chains, Greenleaf Classics, BH8070, 1979 (Box 6)
- Vickers, Robert, Slave Secretary, Greenleaf Classics, BH8113, 1981 (Box 6)
- Vickers, Robert, Tied Up With Sis, Greenleaf Classics, BH8033, 1977 (Box 6)
- Wagner, John, The Horny Housewives, Tai Pan Publications, MB226, n.d. (Box 6)
- Walters, Michael, Horns Up!, Dominion Publishing Co., TNC-330, 1969 (Box 6)
- Warren, Patricia Nell, The Beauty Queen, Bantam Books, 12094-8, 1978 (Box 6)
- Webster, Dan, Abused, Manchester Publications, WLP/110, 1974 (Box 6)
- Wescott, Glenway, Apartment in Athens, Harper & Row, SP353, 1944 (Box 6)
- Wesley, Henry, Sexual Spanking Techniques, Eros Publishing, XL-103, 1976 (Box 6)
- Willow, Peter, Man Maulers, Wee Hours Books, WH 571, 1968 (Box 6)
- Wise, Paul, The Perverted Aryan, Publisher's Consultants, FPS-119, 1979 (Box 6)